https://www.ersc.org/privacy-policy/

Cataract Surgery with Vision-Correcting IOLs
What Is Cataract Surgery with Vision-Correcting IOLsAm I A Candidate For Cataract Surgery With Vision-Correcting IOLsIs Cataract Surgery with Vision-Correcting IOLs Safe
Glossary
What Procedure Is Right For YouInsight: The ERSC Blog
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
YOUR USE OF OUR WEB SITE MEANS THAT YOU AGREE WITH THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY AND AGREEMENT AND ANY OTHER LAW OR REGULATION THAT APPLIES TO THE SITE, THE INTERNET OR THE WORLDWIDE WEB. PLEASE READ THESE TERMS CAREFULLY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THEM, DO NOT USE THIS WEB SITE.PurposeThe American Refractive Surgery Council (“ARSC”, “we” or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy while you visit our Web site. To that end, we have developed the following principles to assure your privacy, as well as protect any information or data you supply to us.Sharing of Your InformationWe will not sell, share, or rent any personal information you supply to us to others except as disclosed in this privacy policy or in connection with specific offers provided to you. We may share your personal information with carefully selected business or affinity partners who have entered into an agreement with ARSC and whose products or services may be of interest to you.Protection of Your InformationPlease note that when you visit our site any data you provide will be transferred to the U.S. where our site is located. ARSC collects personal data about our users to serve their needs, for example, to register visitors for e-mail updates and other features. The information requested depends on the feature offered. We may use the personal information that you provide to respond to your requests for information and to communicate with you about the status of your requests. We respect the information you provide to us and we treat it with reasonable commercial measures.Host Company Data CollectionAs a general matter, each time a visitor or user enters an ARSC Web site, ARSC’s Web site hosting company’s server collects basic technical information, including the visitor’s domain name, e.g., aol.com; referral data, e.g., the last URL a user visited prior to entering ARSC Web sites; and browser and platform type, e.g., Netscape browser or a Macintosh platform. ARSC also tracks and aggregates visitor activity in an analysis of general traffic flow. This information may be aggregated into group data, which then may be shared on an aggregated basis with third parties but, unless otherwise provided for in this policy, ARSC will not disclose individual identity or personal identifiable data without permission.Collection and Use of Personal InformationARSC may collect personal information, such as the user name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, credit card information, password, or login name, in connection with requests for information. All information provided to this site may be available to agents and service providers who help maintain ARSC’s Web sites. The transmission of information to and from us is not encrypted or secure.ARSC reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to safeguard its Web sites, its intellectual property, or the property or safety of others, to investigate violations of this privacy policy and agreement, to cooperate in any legal investigation, or as permitted or required by law.Changes to This AgreementARSC reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy and Agreement or anything else at the site at any time. All users are bound by this Privacy Policy and Agreement and should check this page each time they visit.Special Notice to California ResidentsUnder California’s “Shine the Light” law (SB 27), codified at Section 1798.83 of the Civil Code, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared personal information about you for marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send a letter including the phrase “California Privacy Request” in the subject line, and provide us with your name, address: American Refractive Surgery Council, Attn: Privacy Officer, 999 Corporate Drive, Suite 100, Ladera Ranch, CA 92694. We will respond within thirty days.
Interested in Refractive Surgery?Answers to questions about LASIK, PRK, SMILE and vision-correcting cataract surgery.
